NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Tell your soldiers to retreat.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
I didn't expect you to be here this
soon, Osman.
It's obvious.
If you knew I'd come, you wouldn't have
done what you did.
I have an offer for you, Osman.
Osman!
I'll set your brother and uncle free...
... and in return you'll throw away that
torch.
So, after all, you are okay with dying
with me, Osman!
How about you?
Are you okay with dying with me along with
this dog of yours?
Tell me!
Let's do it like this.
Let's do it step by step.
First throw that...
Osman!
Throw that torch!
Do what I said!
Set my uncle and brother free.
Set them free.
Set them free!
No, Nikola!
Don't let them go!
We shall die all together!
Flatyos...
Dumrul.
Ayaz.
May you set my uncle and brother free.
Now...
Take your soldiers along with Flatyos and
retreat.
Come on!
How are you going to escape here, Osman?
By swinging my arms and hands!
Kill him!
Let's go!
Osman!
Where is Osman?
This isn't the flying fire.
This isn't the flying fire!
He deceived us! It's not the the flying
fire!
Soldier!
Osman!
Come and confront me!
Mount your horses!
Osman!
Ayaz and Dumrul.
May you divert the army of dogs!
As you order, my Bey.
Come on!
Faster!
Don't worry, uncle.
We'll make them pay for everything.
I neither forgot about the dagger stabbed
at the back of my brother, Gündüz...
... nor the one stabbed at your hand.
I will make every single one of them pay!
Every single one of them!
May you live long, my nephew.
May you live long.
You saved us from that dog.
You came...
I came!
I came, uncle!
I had no choice.
I couldn't leave you at the hand of that
dog!
I couldn't trust the warrant of Yalvak
Arslan.
Just like I couldn't trust the mercy of
Nikola.
But how about you?
Tell me, uncle.
Brother.
You will keep trusting them.
You will keep believing in the lies of
that enemy, uncle!
Brother!
Do you know why?
Instead of my factual words...
... you prefer the lies spilled from the
mouth of our enemies!
All must do what's best for them!
Until...
... we don't have any enemies to fight!
Are you bragging, Osman?
You say all must do what's best for them.
Is this what's best for you?
I still haven't started doing what's
best for me.
Uncle!
Brother!
I'm just trying to warn you.
May you go to the Tent now.
Ayaz and Dumrul will escort you.
I have things to do.
It might be a trap! Be careful!
Charge!
Catch them!
I don't want to die.
Don't worry.
Flatyos is merciful.
I will save you.
I saved you from the wrath of living a
dishonorable life.
Because you can't resist that feeling.
Osman!
You!
I didn't see you before.
There will be chaos when the flying fire
explodes.
Then you'll sneak into the castle.
The siege of Kulacahisar has started.
When I go to that castle again...
...instead of fighting, I will take it
this time.
The siege of Kulacahisar has started.
We should hurry up, brother.
We still have a lot to do.
Let's go.
Commander Flatyos!
What's the result?
We lost their track at a narrow pass,
Nikola.
You lost their track.
Am I right?
How did that happen?
They trapped us.
My soldiers died, Nikola.
You got trapped.
And you got my soldiers killed, Flatyos!
This is my castle!
They are my soldiers!
Mine!
Osman killed my soldiers, Flatyos!
My soldiers!
Perhaps you will kill me now, Nikola.
What are you doing, Nikola?
I'm killing you, Flatyos!
You are no longer a commander of Rome.
You are dead now.
From now on, you are nothing.
You are not even a soldier, Flatyos.
Osman Bey, we received news about Geyhatu.
Geyhatu knows that he will deflate
Kulacahisar sooner or later.
So he is going to organize a carnival at
the Tent of Yalvak Arslan.
And they are going to invite you and make
you break the ice with Nikola.
It's fine.
Let them organize their carnival.
Dündar, Savcı, and Gündüz Bey are also
invited.
Geyhatu wants you to obey him.
Geyhatu strugless to learn the fact that
Turks never obey.
He will learn eventually, Osman Bey.
He will.
I won't allow this.
I'm not going to let you die before you
save your own honor!
Flatyos, if you ever try to commit
suicide...
... no clergymen, priest, or pastor will
bury you with religious rituals!
I promise you that!
I hope everything is okay, Davut brother.
What could happen to Dündar and Savcı Bey?
What about them?
They look like they came from Kulacahisar
empty handed.
They should be grateful that they came
back.
I'm going to suggest that...
... nothing have happened there but...
... Osman and his Alps know about
everything.
Neither Osman...
... nor his Alps will say anything,
nephew.
However, I'm just thinking how we will
look at Osman's face ever again.
They say brothers ought to help each other
no matter what happens, uncle.
Perhaps, someday I will save him from a
trouble too.
After that time, debts we'll be paid.
And we will be even.
Debts may be doubled, Savcı Bey.
With Allah's permission, we'll pay them
all one day.
Osman saved you once again.
Who knows where he is right now.
How can I betray him while he tries so
much for his Tent?
Oh, Karayel.
Can you see?
Even Geyhatu understands that I'll take
Kulacahisar.
However, my uncle and brother did not.
Perhaps, Geyhatu also knows that when I
take Kulacahisar...
...no one will dare to stand against me.
However...
... my uncle and brother still don't
get it.
But, eventually they will learn...
... see it...
... and understand it.
And Geyhatu will understand that threats
don't work against me!
May he do his best!
May it be easy, Hatuns.
Thank you.
I'd like to help you if that's okay.
Of course, Targun Hatun!
You've become one of us recently.
Perhaps, someday you will become a bride
of Kayıs.
Inshallah.
A bride of Kayıs?
Is there even a Kayıbeyi who is not
married?
Does he have to be a Bey?
A Bey's daughter must marry a Bey.
There is no Kayıbeyi who is not married.
But there is a Bey who wants to have a
child.
I hope it's for good.
Are you trying to find a Bey for Targun
now?
It’s hard to be a Hatun in Kayı, daughter.
I was hard before. It’s harder now.
Our ancestors had
ruled insignificant lands.
Back then, even Hatuns
like Hazal could marry…
… stupid Beys and become Hatun of Beys.
But now, things are different.
Kayıs are talking about becoming a state.
Being the Hatun of a Kayı Bey…
... means being the Hatun of the state.
For example, my Osman married Bala Hatun.
.. who was raised by Sheikh Edebali.
A Hatun worthy of ruling the world.
What I mean is, if you want
to be a Kayı Hatun…
… or bring a child to the Kayıs…
… try to be a Bala.
Excuse me. I have things to do.
Of course, daughter. Go, and work!
What happened to you, Bey?
Stop and tell me what happened!
Come on. Tell me.
Osman. He was always mad like this.
He was always bold. He was brave.
But he wouldn’t think
about the consequences.
I always thought he would die in a battle
before he got this old.
But he’s braver, bolder,
more consistent by day!
This won’t be easy, Hatun.
Such a man won’t show
mercy for his cause, right?
You know the tradition.
Osman is the youngest of you.
It’s normal that he’s trying harder
to show that he’s in control.
But since our Bey chose you as
the Head Alp, you’re his obstacle.
What do you mean, Hatun?
To be the Kayı’s Bey,
Osman will try to kill you.
What are you saying about
my brother, Hatun?
Your brother won’t do anything
outside the traditions, righT?
But if the traditions allow Osman
to take your head, Osman will take it!
What I’m saying is,
before Osman takes your head-
Enough!
I’ll ignore what you’ve said.
You have to do it, Savcı Bey.
That fire will jump either
on my or Bala’s tent.
You decide whose heart will burn.
I will not shed my brother’s blood!
States are found on blood.
Cerkutay.
Cerkutay…
Now tell me. Who did you try
to trick my Osman with?
Who let the dogs out? Tell me.
I’ll cut you to pieces, Cerkutay.
I’ll feed the dogs with your flesh.
So, Cerkutay, tell me
who you work for.
Don’t play with me, Cerkutay.
This has been going
on for too long.
Let’s not waste any more time then.
Let’s cut it short.
Or should I cut your throat?
I should start with your ears.
First one, then the other.
You’ll still talk, but you
won’t hear a thing you say!
Let’s start with this ear.
Wait!
Yavlak Arslan!
Yavlak Arslan.
What is it Targun Hatun?
Where are you going?
I feel tired.
I’ll rest in my tent.
She’s up to something.
She thinks no one will notice.
Gonca.
Find out where she’s going.
I’ll keep my eyes on her.
Don’t worry.
- My Bey!
- Talk.
Cerkutay talked.
Let’s see who was
playing tricks on us.
Yavlak Arslan. He’s also the one
who had been working with Möngke.
Let no one in
the Tent hear about this.
As you order, my Bey.
I’ll make them pay for this.
Who do you think will
replace Flatyos?
Whoever replaces him will be better.
Who are you to talk about
commander Flatyos? Pity.
Where are my manners?
Let’s go.
This road leads to the castle.
What are you up to,
Targun Hatun?
I’m here for the Landlord.
Brother, isn’t that Targun Hatun?
Her very self!
What is she doing here?
Let’s go, brother.
What are you doing here?
Why arent you in the Tent?
I brought you the information
you asked for.
Let my father our and I’ll leave.
Osman attacked me twice and
I was aware of only one!
But you did what I asked, is that it?
It wasn’t my fault!
Tergun! Osman
is more powerful than before!
Please tell me how your job is done!
I don’t want to do it anymore.
Is that so?
And I don’t want to listen
to your nonsense, Tergun.
I don’t like nonsense.
Show me my father, Nikola.
I must be sure that he’s alive.
Don’t you trust me?
Let me show you your father.
Why don’t you come?!
Bring her.
What is it, my Bala?
Did something happen?
Targun Hatun left the tent, my Bey.
I sent Gonca after her.
She said saw her going to Kulacahisar.
So, she went to Kulacahisar.
Thank you, my Bala.
I’ll deal with the rest.
Why would she go to that castle?
Don’t worry, Bala.
After I conquer that castle,
every malice inside will be gone!
Don’t worry, my Bala.
Then?
You’ll be a Bey. Right, Osman?
Of course, I’ll be a Bey.
Does that make you sad, my Bala?
You need an heir, Osman.
You need a Hatun who
will give you an heir.
It is now time, Osman Bey.
For the future of Kayı,
you need to find a new Hatun.
What are you saying, my Bala?
If you don’t do it
so I’m not sad…
… I’ll find you that Hatun.
Bala!
Father!
Daughter!
Open the door!
- My daughter. - Father!
Open, I said!
Open it.
Come on! Move!
- Father! - My daughter!
Father! Are you okay?
What did you do to my father?
I agree. Should I tell
the guards to be more careful?
You’re alive. Don’t
think about me, daughter.
They want me to betray the Turks, father.
Don’t do it, daughter!
Don’t throw yourself
in the fire to save me.
They are our brothers!
These dogs are nothing to us!
But she has to hold on, right Targun?
Or her father will die.
Let me put it this way, if necessary,
she’ll even sleep with Osman.
Nikola! I will skin you, Nikola!
If I let you live, there
might be a chance. Maybe.
Targun Hatun.
Before there are no more Turks…
… your job won’t be over.
Otherwise, your father dies.
If it’s not enough, you’ll die.
Or I could tell Osman I have a spy.
Then either Osman kills you…
Your choice.
You’ll live, father!
You’ll get out of here
and take our revenge!
When that day comes, I’ll be there.
- I promise.
- Let me go!
I promise! I will take our revenge!
- Father!
- I promise!
You said you’d repair my sword.
Why did you put it there?
Osman Bey’s orders.
I’ll forge new swords.
Your’s might wait for a little.
Who told you mine could wait?
Why shouldn’t it? Kayı
Beys’ Hatuns will relax a little.
They shouldn’t worry. I promised
Selcan Hatun to leave them alone.
Now that’s good news.
You repair my sword
and I’ll forge that steel.
How could a woman forge steel?
Give me that and everyone will see.
Where are you going, Targun Hatun?
Osman Bey! I’m…
I was returning to the Tent.
I see.
I know where you’re going.
Where are you returning from?
What are you up to?
You’re one of those who
will be settled up with!
Allah is one!
Allah is great!
People!
From now on, the days of
‘you can’t do it’ are over.
This is the Tent of Osman bey who’ll be
taking Kulacahisar with a handful of Alps.
Here, everyone will do
what others call impossible!
Good work, master.
It looks like a
real sword now.
Sisters! When it’s about battle…
… you don’t have to wait
for your Beys’ permissions.
When Osman Bey gives the orders,
you’ll take your swords and follow me!
But you need to be trained.
Good luck, master. Thank you.
May my Allah cure her
as soon as possible.
Let’s mind our own
businesses. Let’s go!
What are you up to with Nikola?
Tell me one by one!
I will tell you.
You want to die fighting!
I will die one day.
In my funeral, they’ll call me
‘The woman who killed Osman Bey’!
Of course. Everyone
in your funeral will hear this.
But they’ll hear it from me.
We’ll see.
I know you well.
You don’t attack the unarmed.
Stop this nonsense!
What are you up to with Nikola?
My father…
Don’t be afraid.
You’re safe.
I’ll tell you.
They wanted to meet me.
They had captured my men.
Kurgun!
Güneş! What did they do to you?
How could you do this?
Let them go!
Come and get it.
I’ll rip you apart and
take that key!
I can’t wait, Targun.
Where is my father?
If you want to see your father,
you have to accept Nikola’s offer.
No one threatens us Kuman Turks!
Where is my father, I said!
Targun. If you want to see your
father, you have to deserve it.
Die, degenerate!
You’re as good as Nikola mentioned.
But not that much.
Father!
I want something from you.
You’ll give me Osman, Targun.
I’ll hear and feel every step
he takes and every move he makes…
… with you.
When you give me what I want…
… I’ll give you your father and your men.
Maybe more.
I like rewards.
By the way, these poor
guys didn’t eat anything yet.
If you accept it,
they’ll eat something.
They are about to starve.
Your choice.
You’ll give me Osman, Targun.
What will you do with me?
So, Nikola wanted
me from you.
Let’s give him what he wants.
We heard that Osman Bey
was looking for a new Hatun.
What are you talking about, Hatun?
Since you can’t get pregnant.
Osman will hear about it.
He’ll be embarrassed because of me.
Don’t give up just yet.
It has to have a cure.
Doesn’t matter, Gonca.
I think about Osman.
He has dreams. I don’t want those
dreams to be crushed because of me.
What can you do other than
look for solutions?
I’d sacrifice myself for Osman, Gonca!
You need a Hatun who
will give you an heir Osman.
What are you saying, Bala?
If you don’t, I’ll find
you that Hatun!
Osman is the hope
of every Turk out there.
If it will keep that hope alive, I’ll
watch my Osman marry another Hatun.
I wonder what happened now.
Bala? What happened?
Tell me, Bala.
We said we’d hide
nothing from each other.
I…
I told Osman Bey to…
… find himself another Hatun.
What did Osman Bey say?
He didn’t want to accept it.
He didn’t accept it, Bala!
Don’t worry.
Gonca, as you know
he has to accept it.
And he will.
But I don’t want it.
Bala!
Poor little one. What did you do wrong?
One part of you will always be missing.
You’ll always wonder
if someone is talking about you.
Bala? What happened?
Come, sit. What made you sad?
Neither of us did anything wrong.
This is how the creator wanted.
We have to be patient, Selcan mother.
My Bala. My beautiful daughter.
- Mother!
- Your mother would die for you.
Selcan mother!
I won’t be a mother!
Don’t say that, my Bala.
Do you know what we are looking at, Lena?
What?
The new bride of the Kayı.
You might be right, Hazal Hatun.
Then, Bala's heart will burn.
And your heart will ease. But,
if Osman has a son from that woman...
...what will happen to us?
Think about that, as well.
Mashallah, my girl. You think that
I don't think about that. You are wrong.
Firstly, you should take care of the enemy
that is close. The other is for later.
-Brother.
Geyhatu had sent a word. He wants
you to make peace with Nikola.
What will he do otherwise?
Otherwise, he'll come here with his army,
and destroy the whole place.
We wouldn't want that, brother, right?
Of course not, brother.
What do you think that we should do?
Yavlak Arslan will host both sides.
You will make peace in his presence.
Osman, I say that you
should accept it, brother.
Right, Yavlak Arslan is
the bey of the beys.
Osman, look, we just got
rid of the Mongol trouble.
-Don't.
-Don't worry, brother. Geyhatu won't return here.
Will you accept it?
Will you come together with Nikola?
If Geyhatu wants so.
I didn't think that I could
convince you. Thank you, brother.
-Savcı and my uncle will be happy.
-They should be happy.
-We haven't eaten as a family, for a while.
-Right.
And women are fighting. The tents
should have some peace.
Don't you worry, brother. I'll take care
of that. Good idea.
And in the evening, during dinner,
I'll talk about something important.
All right, brother.
We'll listen to you carefully.
Come on.
The arsenal is behind
that street, brother.
Then it should its gates closed, brother.
It should stay closed until we take
the castle, brother.
You!
-Are you talking to us?
-Yes, I'm talking to you!
Let's hide them.
My bey, Geyhatu made Yavlak Arslan
bey of beys.
Dündar and Savcı Beys are working
with him.
They see the future of the Kayı
in him.
Osman Bey is following his own politics.
He doesn't leave Kulucahisar.
Osman doesn't recognize Yavlak Arslan,
my bey.
Gündüz Bey is with Savcı and
Dündar Beys, mentally...
...but in heart, he is
with Osman Bey.
He is trying to stop his brother
but Osman...
What's happening, Abdurrahman Ghazi?
Is our bey awaken?
My bey wanted me to tell the
situation of the Kayı.
And I'm telling him, maybe
he can hear me.
He can hear. He can hear, surely.
Both his ears and heart
are with us. He hears us.
Brother, you are worried about
how we are? Don't.
We are side by side,
shoulder to shoulder. Thank Allah.
Father...
...tonight, we'll eat together,
as a family.
Just like when you were
with us.
Just like that good days.
Our friends are jealous of our unity,
our enemies are scared.
They can't dare to
sow discontent among us.
We protect your trust well.
Father! The flag that you
put in Söğüt is rising.
Kulucahisar, İnegöl, İznik
and Bursa are waiting.
You brought us from barren land
to here.
We, three brothers...
...will take your flag,
your honorable name...
...from lands to seas.
O' Ghazi's son Ghazi...
...if you hear the voice of
your son Osman...
...know that the flame of holy
war that you started is still alive.
Father.
Lad.
He heard me.
-He heard me.
-He did? Do you say he heard you?
Mashallah to my bey.
Mashallah.
I told him about İznik...
...Bursa and further...
...even more further...
...I told him about the overseas,
Bamsı Bey.
A tear dropped from his eye.
It was like...
...a power passed
from his hand...
...to my hand, Bamsı Bey.
You say that he felt it?
Mashallah to my bey.
Are we ready, Bamsı Bey?
We are, we are, thank Allah.
-Will we take that castle?
-With Allah's approval, yes.
Then, we should be on its
gates at once.
We should, lad. We should.
I'll personally break that gate.
May Allah bless Gündüz Bey.
We brought us together.
You came to my tent,
you brought joy. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, uncle. But since our father
hasn't recovered yet, we are sorrowful.
But if we support each other...
...if we keep our hearts good,
we can pass these difficult days.
-Isn't that so, brother?
-You are right, brother.
What do we have that we can't share
that we can sit and talk two sentences?
I like that. Thank Allah.
Be like this always.
Come on, then.
With the name of Allah.
Osman.
You said that you had something
important to tell us.
Tell us if it's the time, brother.
Dargun Hatun!
So, Osman obeyed Geyhatu's orders
and accepted peace, is that so? Good.
Good. Send the word to Flatyos. He'll kill
Osman on his way to Yavlak Arslan.
As you command.
You called me, Nikola.
Yes, I did. I'm going to Yavlak Arslan's
tents. You'll have the command here.
What if Osman tries another visit?
That sheep shepherd isn't stupid enough
to dare to face Geyhatu.
Are you sure of that? What if he is that
stupid? What if he comes after you leave?
Helen? Do you mean that you can't
protect the castle?
I want to know if you take
that chance or not.
Let's say that Osman comes to the castle
and takes Kulucahisar...
...what will happen then, Helen?
He'll be declared war on Geyhatu.
What'll happen then?
Geyhatu will smash him and
the Kayıs like little bugs.
And we'll fulfill our goals.
Helen, I like every way
of winning.
You do.
Sit, Dargun Hatun.
I thought a lot about it.
A Kayı bey can't be without
a heir.
Dargun Hatun.
Will be my wife from now on.
And she will give me an heir.
Osman Bey made the best decision.
I want it more than anyone for
Osman Bey to have a child.
Inshallah, they can have a son soon.
And no one will have anything else to say.
-Inshallah, inshallah.
Inshallah.
Selcan Hatun, what were you saying?
How does a bride come to the Kayı?
Aygül. My heart is already on fire,
don't fuel it up.
And I have no word for you, Osman.
Tomorrow, I'll come to Yavlak Arslan's
meeting.
But before that, I and Bala will go to
the place that we met with each other.
We'll meet again.
As you wish, Osman.
As you wish.
Then...
Welcome again, my girl.
May Allah make you happy.
Inshallah, you'll have
many children.
Come on. Enjoy your meal.
The secret has been revealed.
The secret of love has been revealed.
The lover's heart is a fire scene.
When love falls in your heart, it destroys
everything.
At that time...
The lover can even pass out.
Lovers, ah lovers.
Only the lovers understands the ones
who lost their lover.
Our Sare mother was infertile.
Hz. Ibrahim didn't complain, but didn't
give up his hope either.
Our Sare mother said:
"Your generation should continue...
but I am infertile...
you should marry a young woman."
That's what she said, little lamb.
That's what she said.
When young woman went in the tent
with Hz. Ibrahim...
Our Sare mother felt strange.
How can she not?
We are coming from a single god,
how can we tolerate duality?
Burning...
When the secrets meet...
My Bala.
Am I interrupting our happiness?
It's not you, Osman.
It's a dagger wound.
That wound would heal
sometimes.
But now it won't heal again.
That's all.
That dagger wounded my heart, Bala.
As I see you pale like this,
I get exhausted.
But...
But remember that...
When Our Sare mother give up her hope,
our Lord granted her with a child.
I know Osman.
Hz Ibrahim was about to sacrifice Ismail.
My Bala.
I won't sacrifice you.
I'd die for you.
- Osman.
- Yes?
I know you are going to Kulucahisar.
What I want from you is to take
me there.
Why is that, my Bala?
Why is that?
Do you...
want to be martyr and be free of
your pains?
I become martyr someday in sha Allah,
Osman.
But I want to witness first.
Witness that you become a Bey, you have
sons to carry your Beyship on.
Bala.
Then you should promise me.
What promise?
You are not going to put yourself in
danger in Kulucahisar.
Don't burn my heart.
Promise?
- Promise?
- Promise, my Osman.
Promise.
Bala...
Do you know why I took you off
commendership, Vladius?
You may think that I should be insulted,
Nicola.
No! Contrarily, I don't think...
that you should be insulted. That's
why I did it in front of everyone's eyes
My dear friend. I wanted everyone to think
that I gave up my hope on you.
Because I am still hopeful, Vladius.
In the mountains, in forests you are
going to live.
You are going to be murderer of
everyone...
whose goes to Kayı Tribe.
Our main objective is that shepherd Osman.
Our second objective is Kayıs.
And the third, Vladius, is the
rest of the Turks.
All of them, Vladius.
All of them.
You are going to kill every one of them!
Are you in, Vladius?
I promise you, Nicola!
Until the end of my life!
Nice.
You can go to your duty now.
I promise you Nicola.
None of the Turks will be happy.
Until Osman dies.
Then I will die in peace.
Geyhatu learned what Osman did.
He is preparing a punishment
with his army.
He contacted me for the last warning.
If Osman and Nicola don't make peace,
he is going to kill them.
Is Geyhatu now talking to Osman?
Why does he say "Nicola and Osman" instead
of Inegol Governor and Kayı Bey?
Because this is their war.
It seems we are not a problem for
Geyhatu.
Yavlar Arslan! We trusted you and went to
that dog's place, we nearly died!
You are going to pay for this eventually.
Maybe not today, but someday.
No one is going to go that castle
to make peace.
When we go to that castle again,
we go for a conquer.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come.
My Bey, it's Nicola.
He wants to come in.
Let him in.
Turkish tent.
I like it.
A nice place to meet.
So?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
You were supposed to be five.
Who is missing?
Who, who, who?!
Hah! It's dark Osman!
Dark Osman is missing.
Why am I not surprised?
If that dog continues talking like that,
I won't care Geyhatu...
and kill him right here!
Nicola! I am trying to fix what you've
done in Kulucahisar.
Can you help me?
Okay good, but it seems to me that
you couldn't convince Osman, again.
Who am I going to make peace with?
Osman Bey has a family issiue.
He'll be late.
Ha?
Did Osman have a family?
Now that we are friends, I want to
learn more about this.
Osman Bey is going to marry
Inal Bey's daughter Targun Hatun.
Tar.. Targun...
Targun Hatun?
That man definitely set his mind on being
Kayı Bey.
Or even maybe Osman wants alliance
with Cuman Turks, hah Savcı Bey?
La hawla wala quwwata illa billahil aliyyil azim.
(There is no power and no strenght except for Allah)
- Have you used it before?
- No, sir.
Do you want me to show you how?
I feel honored.
Only I and Nicola will know that I'm here.
No one else.
And if someone does, he'll die.
Aygül.
What is it, inshallah?
Where are you going?
To war.
- What war is that?
- Osman won't stop till getting Kulucahisar.
And I won't stop until he does.
Aygül!
Let's see how good it is.
Where is she off to again?
I don't care where as long as she leaves.
Come Lena, come.
Let's visit our new bride.
Let's warn her about Bala.
I don't really want to talk about this,
but...
I have a feeling that Osman
won't show up.
Osman will come.
He surely will.
He definitely will.
He can choose not to come,
Yavlak Arslan.
I kept my word.
I came here.
Right, Yavlak Arslan?
Who is going to come
if he doesn't?
Geyhatu will.
What is going to happen then?
No people...
and no tent will be still.
Where are you son?
Where are you?
Osman Bey is coming.
Hay Masha Allah(praise be), my valiant.
Here is the Kayı Bey!
Mashallah(praise be) my daughter.
Mashallah.
Salaimun Aleikum.
Welcome, son.
My Bala.
I will go first.
My valiants that I take with me
want to see me in the front.
You should ride in the back.
Don't worry, my Bey. We are going to fight
together with Bala Hatun
Alps are on their way to the castle.
My Allah!
- Let us be the winners!
- Amin.
- Let us destroy the infidels!
- Amin!
- Let us find our aim!
- Amin.
We are on ou rway to Red Apple.
Let us arrive!
Amin!
A handful Turks here, who are here for
the order the world by your name...
We kneel in front of you...
with the honor they've carried through
their ancestors.
Let us be the winners against
the enemy, my Lord.
Amin.
Even the cruel comes strongly, we won't
be shaken.
We will stand tall like a mountain.
We will shake the ground as we walk, and
shake the sky as we shout.
Because we are the children of...
... Oghuz Khan.
Today, we will take Ulucahisar back and
turn there into an Islamıc city.
We will either return from that castle as
the winners or dead as martyrs.
We will either conquer that castle...
... or ...
... no one from this army will return.
- Allahuekber.
- Can we come in, my Bey?
- Come in, Saltuk Bey.
- My Bey.
- Where is Osman Bey?
- Is there any news?
- No news, my Bey.
What do you mean no news?
- Where is Osman Bey?
- We will find him and inform you, my Bey.
Look everywhere, search everywhere. Go!
Could he have gone to Kulucahisar,
Dündar Bey?
Come on, Osman. Show yourself.
Where are you?
Either a martyr or a ghazi.
- May Allah be with you, brother.
- With you too, brother.
- Come on.
- Where are you headed, Osman Bey?
- To Kulucahisar.
Aren't we worth fighting this battle,
too?
You are too, Gence Bey.
Who can stop a brave man who wants to die
as a martyr?
Thank you.
Let's go.
The Turks broke the wall and got inside!
Here! Hurry up! Come on!
Hurry up! Come on!
What is happening?
What is happening here?
From where they are attacking?
Hurry up! Come on!
Hurry up! Here!
Come on!
From where they are attacking?
Run! Run! Come on!
Come on! Hurry up!
What's happening here?
From where they are attacking?
From where?
They broke the wall and got in!
This is impossible.
This is impossible!
Hey, you! Hey!
Come on, Boran. Come on.
Bring that deaf guy to me!
Don't all of you go to the gate!
Find out what happened and inform me!
Come on, come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Wait until we are relieved...
... you pigs.
Ya Allah!
Beys, I came here with good intentions but
I can't say I'm welcomed friendly here.
I am sick of that man's accusations!
Sick of Geyhatu, peace and all of it!
Savcı Bey!
Savcı Bey calm down.
If you want to keep Kulucahisar, you
have to accept our deal. Otherwise..
Or what?
- Will you announce war?
- Don't confuse me with Osman, Nicola.
I won't come with a few alps.
You are talking to the Head Alp!
I can come with all the valiants of
Kayı tribe and destroy you all over.
What does Head Alp mean actually?
Is it something like Corporal?
Stop this!
There's a Turk inside!
Turks are coming!
Hold the gates!
Göktuğ, now brother! Now!
Stop those Turks!
Stop that one!
Shoot him!
Shoot that dog!
Göktuğ!
My brother!
Archers!
Don't let Kayıs pass!
Kill them all!
Die!
- Allah-u Akbar! (Allah is the greatest)
- Damn it!
Allah-u Akbar! (Allah is the greatest)
Osman!
Damn it!
Göktuğ! Brother!
Allah-u Akbar! (Allah is the greatest)
Göktuğ!
Damn it!
Osman!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com